/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data8_3', {
    title: '8.3 Multiply Mixed Numbers',
    path: '8.3-multiply-mixed-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{2}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\input{3}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{3}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{3}}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{3}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{9}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{2}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{20}}{\\fracstr{9}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{9}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{9}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{7}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{7}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{1}}{\\frac{\\input{31}}{\\input{49}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{7}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{7}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{10}}{\\input{7}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{8}}{\\input{7}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{7}}}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{7}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{80}}{\\str{49}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{80}}{\\str{49}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{1}}{\\frac{\\input{31}}{\\input{49}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{80}}{\\fracstr{49}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{31}}{\\fracstr{49}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{31}}{\\fracstr{49}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{25}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{7}}{\\input{5}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{5}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{77}}{\\str{25}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{77}}{\\str{25}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{25}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{77}}{\\fracstr{25}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{25}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{25}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{6}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{4}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{2}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{2}}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{25}}{\\str{4}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{25}}{\\str{4}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{6}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{4}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{25}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{6}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{6}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{2}}{\\frac{\\input{59}}{\\input{64}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{17}}{\\input{8}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true

                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{17}}{\\str{8}}}{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{187}}{\\str{64}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{187}}{\\str{64}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{2}}{\\frac{\\input{59}}{\\input{64}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{187}}{\\fracstr{64}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{59}}{\\fracstr{64}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{59}}{\\fracstr{64}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{18}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{3}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{3}}}{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{55}}{\\str{18}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{55}}{\\str{18}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{18}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{55}}{\\fracstr{18}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{18}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{18}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{9}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{9}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{6}}{\\frac{\\input{8}}{\\input{27}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{9}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{9}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{26}}{\\input{9}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{19}}{\\input{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{26}}{\\str{9}}}{\\frac{\\str{19}}{\\str{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{494}}{\\str{81}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{494}}{\\str{81}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{6}}{\\frac{\\input{8}}{\\input{27}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{494}}{\\fracstr{81}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{6}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{27}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{6}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{27}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\input{3}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\input{3}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{3}}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{3}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{3}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{10}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{16}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{2}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{7}}{\\input{6}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{21}}{\\input{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}{\\frac{\\str{21}}{\\str{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{147}}{\\str{48}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{49}}{\\str{16}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{3}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{16}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{49}}{\\fracstr{16}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{16}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{16}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{5}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Change the mixed numbers into improper fractions.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{3}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}{\\sign{&nbsp; &times; &nbsp;}}{\\mixed{\\fracstr{1}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{3}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{3}}}{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{121}}{\\str{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Write the fraction as a mixed number.}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{121}}{\\str{24}}}',
                answer: '\\mixed{\\input{5}}{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Divide the numerator by the denominator, then make the quotient the mixed number whole and the remainder the mixed number numerator. \xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{121}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 = \xA0}}}{\\row{\\mixed{\\fracstr{5}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}{\\row{css{\\str{answer:  \xA0}}{label_like margin-left-small}}{css{\\mixed{\\fracstr{5}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}{label_like}}}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
